livescore.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy for LiveScore.com | Live Sport Scores and Updates

### INTRODUCTION

Welcome to the privacy policy of LiveScore Limited ( **“LiveScore”** ).

This privacy policy was last updated on 24 May 2018.

LiveScore respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your information. This privacy policy will inform you as to how we look after your information when you visit our website and/or use our mobile application (“App”) (collectively our “Services”) (regardless of where you visit it from) and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

### 1\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE

#### PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy aims to give you information on how LiveScore collects, uses, discloses, transfers, stores and processes your information when you use our Services, including any data you may provide through your use of our Services. 

This website and our mobile applications as available are not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing information about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements the other policies and is not intended to override them.

LiveScore is responsible for your information (collectively referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy policy). 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us using the details set out in section 11.

#### CONTACT DETAILS

LiveScore Limited, Floor 4, Suite 2, Waterport Place, Gibraltar GX11 1AA.

#### THIRD-PARTY LINKS

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit or third party mobile application you may use.

### 2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

**What information we do not collect:**

We do not collect personal data or sensitive personal data when you use our Services. Personal data means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

Sensitive personal data includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

**So what information do we collect?**

When you use our Services, we collect, store and transfer certain information which does not identify you as an individual but rather identifies the device you use to access our Services such as:

  1. **Technical Data** , including internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, information about operating system, platform and other technologies on the devices you use to access our Services.
  2. **Usage Data** , including information about how you use our website, products and services.
  3. **Device Data:** we collect information from the device you use to access our website and/or App. This includes IP address, device model, device operating system version, LiveScore-installed application version.
  4. **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose which. data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature.

If you use our App, we will be asking if you want to receive push notifications from us. Push notification may include alerts, sounds, icon badges and other information in relation to the use of the App itself. You can choose to allow or reject push notifications being sent to your device. If you do not allow us to send you push notifications, you will be able to use the App, but you may not get the full benefit of its features. You can control your preferences to receive push notifications via your device settings.

### 3\. HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION COLLECTED?

We use different methods to collect information from and about your device including through:

  * **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our Services, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your device, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this information by using cookies and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies or those of our advertising partners (see below). Please see our cookie policy for further details.
  * **Third parties or publicly available sources.** We may receive Technical Data about you from analytics providers based outside the EU such as Google..

### 4. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We will only use your information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your information in the following circumstances:

  * Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
  * Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests, and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
  * Where you have sent your information to us for the purpose of participating in a promotion.

#### REASONS FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR INFORMATION

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your information, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Activity | Type of data | Reasons to use your information  
---|---|---  
To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) |  (a) Usage   
(b) Technical   
(c) Device  |  (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise).   
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation   
To deliver relevant Service content to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of our services to you |  (a) Usage   
(b) Technical   
(c) Device  | (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and to grow our business).  
To deliver relevant advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising |  (a) Usage   
(b) Technical   
(c) Device  | (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to run our business profitably).  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, advertising, customer relationships and experiences. |  (a) Usage   
(b) Technical   
(c) Device  | (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business).  
  
#### COOKIES

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use and how to manage your preferences, please see our cookie policy.

### 5\. DISCLOSURES OF YOUR INFORMATION

Your information will only be disclosed to companies within the LiveScore group of companies and third parties outside those groups in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

LiveScore may transfer your information to another company if it restructures its business. LiveScore may transfer your information to a third party if the operator of the website changes, or if there is a sale of all or any part of its business or its assets. In the event of any of these transfers occurring, the party who acquires the data will assume the rights and obligations described in this privacy policy.

LiveScore may engage the services of third party service providers and suppliers for certain activities including, but not limited to, processing your information and providing technical support to our Services. LiveScore will take steps to ensure that arrangements with third party service providers protect your privacy by ensuring that these third parties comply strictly with instructions when they are processing your information.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third party service providers to use your information for their own purposes and only permit them to process your information for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### 6\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

We do not transfer your information outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

### 7.  OUR ADVERTISING PARTNERS

Some of the ads you receive while using the Services are customised based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to different websites in the browser you use and on other devices you may use. This type of ad customisation is sometimes called "online behavioural" or "interest-based" advertising. Such interest-based advertising helps support the free content, products and services you receive via our Services.

To do so we currently work with: 

  * Oath EMEA Limited and its affiliates including Ad Tech GmbH ([https://privacy.aol.co.uk/advertising-and-privacy/index.html)](https://privacy.aol.co.uk/advertising-and-privacy/index.html),
  * The Rubicon Project, Inc, and its affiliates ([https://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/)](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/),

(together "Ad Partners").

In order to deliver interest-based advertising that is more likely to be relevant to you, we deploy cookies, web beacons and similar technologies built by such Ad Partners that collect usage data, namely the IP address of your device and the websites visited using that device. Ad Partners then receive such usage data and use it to deliver the advertising of the Ad Partner's advertisers. The Ad Partners do not receive any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or contact details. Please refer to the Ad Partner's respective privacy policies (via the above links) for more information on how their services work.

If you not want our Ad Partners to receive such usage data or you do not want to receive such interest-based advertising, please follow the instructions at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>, [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or [http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) in order to manage preferences via your browser if you are visiting the website. If you are using the mobile app, you can manage preferences via your device's privacy setting (e.g., Apple iOS Limit Ad Tracking).

If you do not want our Ad Partners to receive such usage data or you do not want to receive such interest-based advertising, please follow the instructions If you do not want our Ad Partners to receive such usage data or you do not want to receive such interest-based advertising, please follow the instructions 

We adhere to the self-regulatory principles of the Network Advertising Initiative Network Advertising Initiative (<https://www.networkadvertising.org/>), Digital Advertising Alliance (<https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/>), and European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (<https://www.edaa.eu/>) insofar as they are applicable to website operators.

### 8\. DATA SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your information to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need-to-know. They will only process your information on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

### 9\. DATA RETENTION

#### HOW LONG WILL YOU USE MY INFORMATION FOR?

We will only retain your information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for (e.g. such as providing you access to our Services), including for the purpose of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. If you want to know how long we retain information collected via the use of cookies read our cookie policy.

### 10\. YOUR RIGHTS

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data, including the right to:

  * Request access to your personal data.
  * Request correction of your personal data.
  * Request erasure of your personal data.
  * Object to processing of your personal data.
  * Request restriction of processing your personal data.
  * Request transfer of your personal data.
  * Right to withdraw consent.

We do not hold or store any of your personal data via our Services. However, our Ad Partners do collect and use the usage data described in Section 7 above. **If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above in respect of such data, please contact the Ad Partners using the details in their privacy policy.**

### 11\. QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us here.

Update consent
